Guide to the William Rose Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1897-1955; 1922-1950; Series I; 22.43; 50 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Maslenikov, Oleg A., 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1117)
    - Mason, Daniel Gregory, 1944; 1947 (Box 29, Folder 1118)
    - Mason, Walter Scott, undated (Box 29, Folder 1119)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1934 March 7 (Box 29, Folder 1120)
    - Masters, Joseph G., 1949 February (Box 29, Folder 1121)
    - Masters, Marcia, 1947, undated (Box 29, Folder 1122)
    - Mastin, Florence Ripley, 1947–1950 (Box 29, Folder 1123)
    - Matchett, William H., 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1124)
    - Mathison, Richard, 1948–1950 (Box 29, Folder 1125)
    - Matthiessen, F. O. (Francis Otto), 1948-1950, undated (Box 29, Folder 1126)
    - Maurois, André, 1942-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1127)
    - Mawson, Christian, 1941 November 26 (Box 29, Folder 1128)
    - Maxwell, Gilbert, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1129)
    - May, Stephen, 1946 February 4 (Box 29, Folder 1130)
    - Mayberry, George, 1944; 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1131)
    - Mayfield, John S., 1927; 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1132)
    - Maynard, Theodore, 1941–1948 (Box 29, Folder 1133)
    - Mearns, Hughes, 1949–1950 (Box 29, Folder 1134)
    - Meeker, Arthur, 1942 January 28 (Box 29, Folder 1135)
    - The Meeting Place, 1929–1930 (Box 29, Folder 1136)
    - Meigs, Dwight R., 1906-1907, undated (Box 29, Folder 1137)
    - Mellon, Evelyn Emig, 1928 December 20 (Box 29, Folder 1138)
    - Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1935–1949 (Box 29, Folder 1139)
    - Merrill, Charles, 1934 November 19 (Box 29, Folder 1140)
    - Merrill, James, undated (Box 29, Folder 1141)
    - Merrill, Maud M., 1946-1950, undated (Box 29, Folder 1142)
    - Merritt, Jesse, 1943-1949, undated (Box 29, Folder 1143)
    - Map (copy) removed from Merrit, Jesse, undated (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3331)
    - Metcalfe, John, 1930–1949 (Box 29, Folder 1144)
    - Methuen Co., 1935 June 13 (Box 29, Folder 1145)
    - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, 1941 September (Box 29, Folder 1146)
    - Meyer, Gerard Previn, 1946–1950 (Box 29, Folder 1147)
    - Michaelson, L. W., 1949 June 8 (Box 30, Folder 1148)
    - Miles, Josephine, 1939, undated (Box 30, Folder 1149)
    - Miles, Nadine, 1949, undated (Box 30, Folder 1150)
    - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1921-1949, undated (Box 30, Folder 1151)
    - Miller, Benjamin, 1928–1933 (Box 30, Folder 1152)
    - Miller, Lois M., 1949 August 20 (Box 30, Folder 1153)
    - Miller, Marvin, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 1154)
    - Miller, Vassar, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 1155)
    - Mills College, 1936 June 30 (Box 30, Folder 1156)
    - Milwaukee Public Library, 1944 April (Box 30, Folder 1157)
    - Miner, Virginia Scott, 1943–1950 (Box 30, Folder 1158)
    - Mitchell, Howard T., 1949 (Box 30, Folder 1159)
    - Mitchell, MacNeil, 1945 March 5 (Box 30, Folder 1160)
    - Modern Language Quarterly, 1950 March 15 (Box 30, Folder 1161)
    - Moir, Phyllis, 1948 February (Box 30, Folder 1162)
    - Molk, Sophia, 1950 March 30 (Box 30, Folder 1163)
    - Moloney, Gene, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 1164)
    - Montgomery, Elizabeth Shaw, [?] November 28 (Box 30, Folder 1165)
    - Moody, William Vaughn, 1907 January 16 (Box 30, Folder 1166)
    - Moon, Mary, 1947, undated (Box 30, Folder 1167)
    - Moore, Donald J., 1949–1950 (Box 30, Folder 1168)
    - Moore, Douglas; Moore, Emily, 1929-1950, undated (Box 30, Folder 1169)
    - Moore, John G., 1942–1949 (Box 30, Folder 1170)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1933-1954, undated (Box 30, Folder 1171-1172)
    - Moore, Merrill, 1935-1949, undated (Box 30, Folder 1173)
    - Moore, Virginia, 1934 July 29 (Box 30, Folder 1174)
    - Moore, Warner, 1943 March 18 (Box 30, Folder 1175)
    - Moravian Seminary and College for Women, 1947 November (Box 30, Folder 1176)
    - Morcom, [James Stewart?], 1943 May 23 (Box 30, Folder 1177)
    - Morley, Christopher; Morley, Helen, 1923–1949 (Box 30, Folder 1178-1181)
    - Morley, Christopher; Morley, Helen, 1949-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 1182-1183)
    - Morley, S. G[riswold?], 1935 August 5 (Box 31, Folder 1184)
    - Morrill, Belle Chapman, 1945 June 20 (Box 31, Folder 1185)
    - Morris, Lloyd [R.?], 1928; 1944 (Box 31, Folder 1186)
    - Morse, Richard Ely, 1928; 1934 (Box 31, Folder 1187)
    - Morton, David, 1947–1950 (Box 31, Folder 1188)
    - Morton, Ruth, 1950 March (Box 31, Folder 1189)
    - Moses, Robert, 1945; 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1190)
    - Motive, 1947-1949, undated (Box 31, Folder 1191)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1948 March 27 (Box 31, Folder 1192)
    - Moylan, Charita M., 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1193)
    - Mukerj, Kamala, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 1194)
    - Mulholland, John F[ield?], 1945 November 13 (Box 31, Folder 1195)
    - Mullins, Helene, undated (Box 31, Folder 1196)
    - Murphy, Joseph Francis, 1949, undated (Box 31, Folder 1197)
    - Murray, Pauli, 1947-1948, undated (Box 31, Folder 1198)
    - Myers, Richard E., 1927-1949, undated (Box 31, Folder 1199)
    - "N" general, 1905-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 1200-1201)
    - N.W. Ayer Son, 1944 February 11 (Box 31, Folder 1202)
    - Nash, Ogden, 1931 November 5 (Box 31, Folder 1203)
    - Nathan, Robert, 1923-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 1204)
    - The Nation, 1944; 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1205)
    - National Arts Club (New York, N.Y.), 1948 November (Box 31, Folder 1206)
    - National Association of Secondary School Principals (U.S.), 1946 February 1 (Box 31, Folder 1207)
    - National Audubon Society, 1948 August (Box 31, Folder 1208)
    - National Child Labor Committee, 1943 November 10 (Box 31, Folder 1209)
    - National Citizens Political Action Committee, 1944 September 6 (Box 31, Folder 1210)
    - National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax, 1943 June 16 (Box 31, Folder 1211)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 1212)
    - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship (U.S.), 1946 April 26 (Box 31, Folder 1213)
    - National Council of Teachers of English, 1942–1943 (Box 31, Folder 1214)
    - The National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1929; 1948 (Box 31, Folder 1215)
    - National Fantasy Fan Federation, 1944–1945 (Box 31, Folder 1216)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.), 1935-1950, undated (Box 31, Folder 1217-1218)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1943 July 26 (Box 31, Folder 1219)
    - National League of American Penwomen, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 1220)
    - National Liberal Club (London, England) (to Elinor Wylie), 1927 December 9 (Box 31, Folder 1221)
    - National Parent-Teacher, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 1222)
    - National War Fund, 1945 June 15 (Box 31, Folder 1223)
    - Nauman, Spencer G[ilbert], 1946 February (Box 31, Folder 1224)
    - Nebel, Frederick, 1936 January 18 (Box 31, Folder 1225)
    - Neel, Samuel E. [(Samuel Ellison)?], 1948–1949 (Box 32, Folder 1226)
    - Nef, Evelyn Stefansson, 1942, undated (Box 32, Folder 1227)
    - Neihardt, John Gneisenau, 1933–1944 (Box 32, Folder 1228)
    - Nelson, Selma, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 1229)
    - Nelson, Starr, 1943, undated (Box 32, Folder 1230)
    - Nettleton, Mary Glover, 1949-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 1231)
    - Neuberger, Richard L., 1949 August 10 (Box 32, Folder 1232)
    - Neuman, Irene F., 1943–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1233)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1947 December 20 (Box 32, Folder 1234)
    - The New Athenaeum, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1235)
    - New England Poetry Club, 1949, undated (Box 32, Folder 1236)
    - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1943 September 15 (Box 32, Folder 1237)
    - The New Leader, 1950 January (Box 32, Folder 1238)
    - New Masses, 1936–1945 (Box 32, Folder 1239)
    - The New Quarterly of Poetry, 1947, undated (Box 32, Folder 1240)
    - The New Republic, 1923-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 1241)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1929-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 1242)
    - New York Mirror, 1944 June 15 (Box 32, Folder 1243)
    - New York Public Library, 1924–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1244)
    - New York Society Library, 1943 December 3 (Box 32, Folder 1245)
    - New York (State). Department of Taxation and Finance, 1929 December 26 (Box 32, Folder 1246)
    - New York Telephone Company, 1949 February (Box 32, Folder 1247)
    - New York Times, 1940–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1248)
    - New York World Telegram, 1948, undated (Box 32, Folder 1249)
    - The New Yorker, 1930-1949, undated (Box 32, Folder 1250)
    - Newbolt, Henry John, Sir, 1928-1930, undated (Box 32, Folder 1251)
    - Newmeyer, Sarah, 1949 September (Box 32, Folder 1252)
    - Nicholl, Louise Townsend, 1942-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 1253)
    - Nichols, Dudley, 1929, undated (Box 32, Folder 1254)
    - Nicholson, Watson, 1927 January 12 (Box 32, Folder 1255)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1950 March (Box 32, Folder 1256)
    - Nielson, Veneta Leatham, 1950 January (Box 32, Folder 1257)
    - Nims, John Frederick, 1944–1949 (Box 32, Folder 1258)
    - Nizer, Louis, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 1259)
    - Noon, Louisa Hawley, 1944–1945 (Box 32, Folder 1260)
    - Norton, D. E.; Norton, Maud, undated (Box 32, Folder 1261)
    - Norton, Polly Lois, 1937-1944, undated (Box 32, Folder 1262)
    - Nott, Stanley, 1928 January 31 (Box 32, Folder 1263)
    - Novák, Sonia Ruthèle, 1930, undated (Box 32, Folder 1264)
    - Noyes, Alfred, 1947–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1265)
    - "O" general, 1926-1950, undated (Box 32, Folder 1266)
    - Ó Faracháin, Roibeárd, 1949 October 7 (Box 32, Folder 1267)
    - Obear, Emily Hanson, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 1268)
    - O'Brien, Katherine, 1948–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1269)
    - O'Brien, Maxine, 1948-1949, undated (Box 32, Folder 1270)
    - O'Brien, May, 1946, undated (Box 32, Folder 1271)
    - O'Connor, William Van, 1948–1949 (Box 32, Folder 1272)
    - O'Conor, Norreys Jephson, 1948–1950 (Box 32, Folder 1273)
    - O'Donnell, George Marion, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1274)
    - O'Dwyer, William, 1946 December 27 (Box 33, Folder 1275)
    - Odyssey Press, 1947 March 12 (Box 33, Folder 1276)
    - Oehser, Paul H. (Paul Henry), 1946; 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1277)
    - Oenslager, Donald, 1948-1949, undated (Box 33, Folder 1278)
    - O'Halloran, Elspeth, undated (Box 33, Folder 1279)
    - O'Hara, John, 1948 December (Box 33, Folder 1280)
    - O'Hara, John Myers, 1930, undated (Box 33, Folder 1281)
    - Old Colony Trust Company (Boston, Mass.), 1948–1949 (Box 33, Folder 1282)
    - Old Lyme-Phoebe Griffin Noyes Library (Old Lyme, Conn.), 1947 May (Box 33, Folder 1283)
    - Old Settler Book Shop, 1945–1949 (Box 33, Folder 1284)
    - Oliver, Edith, [1925?]-1943, undated (Box 33, Folder 1285)
    - Oliver-Smith, Martha, 1942-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 1286)
    - Olson, Eric George, 1949–1950 (Box 33, Folder 1287)
    - Opalov, Leonard, 1941-1943, undated (Box 33, Folder 1288)
    - Orage, A. R. (Alfred Richard), 1928–1929 (Box 33, Folder 1289)
    - Orr, Hugh Robert, 1946 February 18 (Box 33, Folder 1290)
    - Ortmayer, Roger, 1944 December 5 (Box 33, Folder 1291)
    - Osborn, Minott, 1908-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 1292)
    - Letter removed from Osborn, Minott, 1908 September 18 (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3332)
    - Osborn, Stellanova, 1944 June 17 (Box 33, Folder 1293)
    - Osborne, Kelsie Ramey, 1949 August 30 (Box 33, Folder 1294)
    - O'Sheel, Shaemas, 1942; 1948 (Box 33, Folder 1295)
    - Otis, Arthur Frederic, 1947–1950 (Box 33, Folder 1296)
    - Overstreet, Bonaro W. (Bonaro Wilkinson), 1944; 1948 (Box 33, Folder 1297)
    - Oxford University Press, 1929-1947, undated (Box 33, Folder 1298)
    - "P" general, 1928-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 1299-1301)
    - Pacific Monthly, 1907–1909 (Box 33, Folder 1302)
    - Pacific Northwest Writers' Conference, 1948 January 9 (Box 33, Folder 1303)
    - Page, Curtis C., 1949 December (Box 33, Folder 1304)
    - Paget, Richard Arthur Surtees, Sir, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 1305)
    - Pagnini, Marcello, 1947-1948, undated (Box 33, Folder 1306)
    - Pan American Union, 1944 April (Box 33, Folder 1307)
    - Paquette, Donald J., 1950 January (Box 33, Folder 1308)
    - Park, Clyde W. (Clyde William), 1949 July (Box 33, Folder 1309)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1948 March 10 (Box 33, Folder 1310)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1949-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 1311)
    - Parker, Maude, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 1312)
    - Parker, Robert Allerton, 1946 March (Box 33, Folder 1313)
    - Parkes, Dow, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1314)
    - Parkhurst, Winthrop, 1943 August 5 (Box 33, Folder 1315)
    - Partridge, Ruth Louise, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 1316)
    - Partlan, Anne, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 1317)
    - Patchen, Kenneth, 1947-1948, undated (Box 33, Folder 1318)
    - Pearce, Helen, 1929 February (Box 34, Folder 1319)
    - Pearson, Edmund L[ester?], 1929, undated (Box 34, Folder 1320)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1936-1950, undated (Box 34, Folder 1321-1322)
    - Peat, Harold R. (Harold Reginald), 1935; 1940 (Box 34, Folder 1323)
    - Peattie, Donald Culross, 1941 January 17 (Box 34, Folder 1324)
    - Peck, Robert Grey, 1948-1949, undated (Box 34, Folder 1325)
    - Pedler, Margaret, 1929 May 2 (Box 34, Folder 1326)
    - Peikon, June, 1949 July (Box 34, Folder 1327)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1926-1946, undated (Box 34, Folder 1328)
    - Pendrell, Ernest, 1946; 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1329)
    - Pennant, Edmund, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1330)
    - Pennington, Levi T. (Levi Talbott), 1949 (Box 34, Folder 1331)
    - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, 1948 April (Box 34, Folder 1332)
    - Perrine, Laurence, 1940 April (Box 34, Folder 1333)
    - Perry, Bliss, 1929 March (Box 34, Folder 1334)
    - Peters, Mary Eleanor, 1944; 1947 (Box 34, Folder 1335)
    - Petite, Irving, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 1336)
    - Petrov, Vladimir N., 1950 May (Box 34, Folder 1337)
    - Pettit, Millicent, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1338)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1943, undated (Box 34, Folder 1339)
    - The Philadelphia Inquirer, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 1340)
    - Philadelphia Record, 1942 July 29 (Box 34, Folder 1341)
    - Piercy, Josephine Ketcham, 1928–1929 (Box 34, Folder 1342)
    - Pilkington, Walter, 1942 March 31 (Box 34, Folder 1343)
    - Pinchot, Ben, 1950 June 10 (Box 34, Folder 1344)
    - Piney Woods School, 1946 March 18 (Box 34, Folder 1345)
    - Piper, Raymond Frank, 1950 March (Box 34, Folder 1346)
    - Pipes, James, 1943, undated (Box 34, Folder 1347)
    - Pleasant, Richard, 1950 January (Box 34, Folder 1348)
    - Plimpton, Harriet, 1948–1949 (Box 34, Folder 1349)
    - Plutzik, Hyram, 1941–1949 (Box 34, Folder 1350)
    - Poet Lore, undated (Box 34, Folder 1351)
    - Poetry, 1921–1950 (Box 34, Folder 1352)
    - The Poetry ChapBook, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 1353)
    - Poetry Review, 1944-1945, undated (Box 34, Folder 1354)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1944-1950, undated (Box 34, Folder 1355)
    - Poets' Corner, Inc., 1946–1947 (Box 34, Folder 1356)
    - Poiret, Paul, 1928 March 8 (Box 34, Folder 1357)
    - Poland, Orville S., 1949 July 1 (Box 34, Folder 1358)
    - Pope, Arthur Upham, 1943 April 6 (Box 34, Folder 1359)
    - Pope, John Alexander, 1948 February (Box 34, Folder 1360)
    - Popular Publications, Inc., 1944–1950 (Box 34, Folder 1361)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1947 June 10 (Box 34, Folder 1362)
    - Porter, Kenneth W., 1939-1948, undated (Box 34, Folder 1363)
    - Porter, Quincy, 1943–1944 (Box 34, Folder 1364)
    - Porterfield, Allen W. (Allen Wilson), 1947 November 11 (Box 34, Folder 1365)
    - Posgate, Mabel, 1942–1950 (Box 34, Folder 1366)
    - Poteat, Edwin McNeill, 1939-1949, undated (Box 34, Folder 1367)
    - Potter, Sheldon, Mrs., 1947, undated (Box 34, Folder 1368)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1928-1933, undated (Box 34, Folder 1369)
    - Powell, Lawrence Clark, 1932–1933 (Box 34, Folder 1370)
    - Powell, William S., 1941 December 16 (Box 34, Folder 1371)
    - Powys, Littleton; Powys, Elizabeth Llewelyn, 1927-1950, undated (Box 34, Folder 1372)
    - Pratt, E. J., 1943–1950 (Box 35, Folder 1373)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1949 (Box 35, Folder 1374)
    - Price, Allan, 1941 December 26 (Box 35, Folder 1375)
    - Primavera Press, 1947 February (Box 35, Folder 1376)
    - Princeton University Press, 1944 September 29 (Box 35, Folder 1377)
    - Prokosch, Frederic, undated (Box 35, Folder 1378)
    - Prouty, Rachel V., 1949 (Box 35, Folder 1379)
    - Publisher's Weekly, 1944 December 5 (Box 35, Folder 1380)
    - Pulitzer, Ralph, 1928–1929 (Box 35, Folder 1381)
    - Pulsifier, Harold T.; [Pulsifier?], Susan, 1943-1948, undated (Box 35, Folder 1382)
    - Punch, 1927 December 28 (Box 35, Folder 1383)
    - Purdy, Theodore, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 1384)
    - Purnell, Idella, 1929; 1950 (Box 35, Folder 1385)
    - "Q" general, 1950 January (Box 35, Folder 1386)
    - "R" general, 1905-1950, undated (Box 35, Folder 1387-1391)
    - Raile, Henry; Raile, Vilate, 1938–1946 (Box 35, Folder 1392)
    - Raine, Alice, 1942 March 24 (Box 35, Folder 1393)
    - Raley, Loker, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 1394)
    - Ranck, Edwin Carty, 1927–1935 (Box 35, Folder 1395)
    - Randall, Frances Ames, 1943–1944 (Box 35, Folder 1396)
    - Random House (Firm), 1929–1950 (Box 35, Folder 1397)
    - Ransom, John Crowe, 1948 January (Box 35, Folder 1398)
    - Ray, Randolph, 1950 May 25 (Box 35, Folder 1399)
    - The Reader's Digest, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 1400)
    - Readio, Bill, 1942; 1949 (Box 35, Folder 1401)
    - The Red Book, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 1402)
    - Redding, J. Saunders (Jay Saunders), 1948–1949 (Box 35, Folder 1403)
    - Redman, Ben Ray, 1929–1950 (Box 35, Folder 1404)
    - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, 1924–1932 (Box 35, Folder 1405)
    - Reilly, Hugh, 1945, undated (Box 35, Folder 1406)
    - Remnek, Martin, 1947 December (Box 35, Folder 1407)
    - Rex, Barbara, undated (Box 35, Folder 1408)
    - Reynard, Grant T., 1941 September 10 (Box 35, Folder 1409)
    - Reynolds, Earle, 1945 June 21 (Box 35, Folder 1410)
    - Reynolds, J. Herbert, 1929–1930 (Box 35, Folder 1411)
    - Reynolds, James, 1947, undated (Box 35, Folder 1412)
    - Reynolds, Quentin [James?], 1940 October 12 (Box 35, Folder 1413)
    - Rhodes, Eugene [Manlove?], undated (Box 35, Folder 1414)
    - Rice, Virginia, 1930-1950, undated (Box 35, Folder 1415)
    - Richards, Grant, 1924 February 16 (Box 36, Folder 1416)
    - Richards, Laura Elizabeth Howe, undated (Box 36, Folder 1417)
    - Richardson, Dorothy Lee, 1947; 1950 (Box 36, Folder 1418)
    - Richart, Bette, 1933-1946, undated (Box 36, Folder 1419)
    - Rickett, Edmond W., 1943 February 9 (Box 36, Folder 1420)
    - Rideout, Francis R., 1942-1950, undated (Box 36, Folder 1421)
    - Ridge, Lola; Lawson, David, 1928-1946, undated (Box 36, Folder 1422)
    - Rigney, William J., 1945 March 28 (Box 36, Folder 1423)
    - Rinehart Company, Inc., 1950 February 8 (Box 36, Folder 1424)
    - Rittenhouse, Jessie B. (Jessie Belle), 1923-1949, undated (Box 36, Folder 1425)
    - Robbins, Leonard J., 1944–1949 (Box 36, Folder 1426)
    - Roberts, Elizabeth Sim, 1949, undated (Box 36, Folder 1427)
    - Roberts, Harriet, 1927-1944, undated (Box 36, Folder 1428)
    - Roberts, Lester, 1945 January 26 (Box 36, Folder 1429)
    - Roberts, Reily Aetizer, 1945; 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1430)
    - Robertson, Clyde, 1938 October 29 (Box 36, Folder 1431)
    - Robeson, Paul, 1944, undated (Box 36, Folder 1432)
    - Robins, Ted, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 1433)
    - Robinson, Corinne Roosevelt, undated (Box 36, Folder 1434)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1923–1934 (Box 36, Folder 1435)
    - Robinson, Martha, 1947–1950 (Box 36, Folder 1436)
    - Rochester Public Library (Rochester, N.Y.), 1941 January 14 (Box 36, Folder 1437)
    - Rodman, Selden, 1927-1949, undated (Box 36, Folder 1438)
    - Roethke, Theodore, 1942-1948, undated (Box 36, Folder 1439)
    - Rogers, Fan, undated (Box 36, Folder 1440)
    - Rolfe, Edwin, 1946–1950 (Box 36, Folder 1441)
    - Rolfe, John, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1442)
    - Rollins, William, 1930 May (Box 36, Folder 1443)
    - Rollins College (Winter Park, Fla.), 1948 September 29 (Box 36, Folder 1444)
    - Romig, Edgar Franklin, 1944 October 23 (Box 36, Folder 1445)
    - Rondeau, Mary R., 1950 (Box 36, Folder 1446)
    - Roof, Simons, 1944–1947 (Box 36, Folder 1447)
    - Root, Katharine Metcalf, undated (Box 36, Folder 1448)
    - Rose, Donald F[rank?], 1929 January 22 (Box 36, Folder 1449)
    - Rose, Ernestine, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 1450)
    - Rose, R. Selden (Robert Selden), 1930, undated (Box 36, Folder 1451)
    - Rosen, Lucie, undated (Box 36, Folder 1452)
    - Rosenberg, James L., 1949 (Box 36, Folder 1453)
    - Ross, Norman, 1946–1948 (Box 36, Folder 1454)
    - Rosten, Norman, 1945-1946, undated (Box 36, Folder 1455)
    - Rothenstein, John, undated (Box 36, Folder 1456)
    - Rourke, Constance, 1926 March 10 (Box 36, Folder 1457)
    - Rowland, Martha Keller, 1944–1950 (Box 36, Folder 1458)
    - Roxburghe Club of San Francisco, 1945 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 1459)
    - Roy, Andrew T. [(Andrew Tod)?], 1948 June 14 (Box 36, Folder 1460)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1943-1950, undated (Box 36, Folder 1461)
    - Runciman, [Ernest?] (to Elinor Wylie), 1926 September 26 (Box 36, Folder 1462)
    - Runciman, Steven, 1927–1929 (Box 36, Folder 1463)
    - Russell, Ada, 1929–1941 (Box 36, Folder 1464)
    - Russell, David, 1946–1947 (Box 36, Folder 1465)
    - Russo, Lola, 1947–1950 (Box 36, Folder 1466)
    - Ryerson Press, 1946; 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1467)
    - Ryman, Sunshine Dickinson, 1937 March 16 (Box 36, Folder 1468)
    - "S" general, 1922-1950, undated (Box 37, Folder 1469-1475)
    - Sabin, Edwin L. (Edwin Legrand), 1946 September 16 (Box 37, Folder 1476)
    - Sable, Barbara Kinsey, 1948 October (Box 37, Folder 1477)
    - Sagarin, Edward, 1948 January (Box 37, Folder 1478)
    - St. Clair, Margaret, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1479)
    - St. Louis Globe-Democrat, 1929 February (Box 37, Folder 1480)
    - St. Nicholas, 1909 June 30 (Box 37, Folder 1481)
    - St. Stephen's College (Annandale-on-Hudson, N.Y.), 1926 March 27 (Box 37, Folder 1482)
    - Sakellariadis, Judith Grant, 1949–1950 (Box 37, Folder 1483)
    - Salomon, Isadore Lawrence, 1946–1950 (Box 37, Folder 1484-1486)
    - Salomon, Joanne, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1487)
    - Salt, George E[dward?], 1947 (Box 37, Folder 1488)
    - Salter, Katharine Hayden, 1936 June 2 (Box 37, Folder 1489)
    - Saltzman, Eleanor, 1943 March 14 (Box 37, Folder 1490)
    - Salz, Ansley K., Mrs., 1950, undated (Box 37, Folder 1491)
    - Sampron, Harriet, 1935 June 9 (Box 37, Folder 1492)
    - Sancton, Thomas, 1947 February 19 (Box 37, Folder 1493)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1931–1949 (Box 37, Folder 1494)
    - Sandoz, Mari, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 1495)
    - Sanford, Hugh Wheeler, 1946 April 30 (Box 37, Folder 1496)
    - Sarah Lawrence College, 1935; 1942 (Box 37, Folder 1497)
    - Sarett, Lew, 1930; 1933 (Box 37, Folder 1498)
    - Saroyan, William, 1934, undated (Box 37, Folder 1499)
    - Sarton, May, 1937–1948 (Box 38, Folder 1500)
    - Sassoon, Babette; Sassoon, W. E., 1946–1950 (Box 38, Folder 1501)
    - Satterfield, Frances G[ibson?], 1929 (Box 38, Folder 1502)
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1935-1954, undated (Box 38, Folder 1503-1510)
    - Saunders, Henry Scholey, 1920; 1922 (Box 38, Folder 1511)
    - Savile Club, 1930 March 4 (Box 38, Folder 1512)
    - Saxon, Lyle, 1929 February 6 (Box 38, Folder 1513)
    - Saxton, [Eugene]; Saxton, Martha, undated (Box 38, Folder 1514)
    - Schappes, Morris U. (Morris Urman), 1948 May 19 (Box 38, Folder 1515)
    - Schealer, John M., 1948; 1950 (Box 38, Folder 1516)
    - Schell, Sherril, undated (Box 38, Folder 1517)
    - Schmalz, Julia Moody, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 1518)
    - Schneider, Isidor, undated (Box 38, Folder 1519)
    - Schocken Books, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 1520)
    - Scholastic, 1943–1946 (Box 38, Folder 1521)
    - Schroeder, Ralph L., 1943–1949 (Box 38, Folder 1522)